Guide to the Cindy Domingo Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Cindy Domingo papers, 1978-2010; 5651-001; 18.92 cubic feet 19 boxes
  - CINDY DOMINGO PAPERS, SERIES I (Box-folder Box 1-Box 19)
    - Civil Rights Bill of 1991, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - Contacts- Congress, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Correspondence from LELO, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 10/20)
    - Correspondence to LELO, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 10/21)
    - Donatations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - Events, 1992 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - Funding, 1993 (Box-folder 10/24)
    - Fundrasing, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Mailing Lists, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 10/26)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) List, Undated (Box-folder 10/27)
    - Clippings, Justice for Ward Cove Workers Act, 1973-1991 (Box-folder 10/28)
    - Labor Summer School for High School Students, July 1992 (Box-folder 10/29)
    - International District Alliance Picture, c. 1970s-c. 1980s (Box-folder 11/1)
    - 1952 Yearbook Cannery Workers (Box-folder 11/2)
    - Eastern Hotel Historic Display Project, 1994-1998 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - 1997 Proposal (Box-folder 11/4)
    - Eastern Hotel Historic Display Project Notes, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 11/5)
    - Carlos Bulosan Memorial Project, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - Carlos Bulosan Memorial Project Details, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 11/7)
    - Bulosan Program Committee Meeting, 1998 (Box-folder 11/8)
    - Program Plans, 1998 (Box-folder 11/9)
    - Bulosan, Carlos, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 11/10)
    - Philippine Temptation, 1972-1999 (Box-folder 11/11)
    - Allied Art Proposal, 1998 (Box-folder 11/12)
    - SouthEast Effective Development postcard and IBM Diskette with notes: View on PageMaker 6.5 'Bulosan Image for Letterhead', 1998 (Box-folder 11/13)
    - Articles on International District, 1976-1999 (Box-folder 11/14)
    - Articles, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 11/15)
    - Carlos Bulosan Memorial Project (2), 1995-1999 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - Alaskero Oral History Text, 1986 (Box-folder 11/17)
    - Publication: La Tormenta Perfecta + Peace and Freedom Magazine, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - EveryWoman's Delegation, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - Evaluation, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - EveryWoman's Delegation 2000, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - 2001 Delegation (Box-folder 12/5)
    - Applications- Cuba, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 12/6)
    - Delegation Details, 2001 (Box-folder 12/7)
    - 2001 Delegation Media, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 12/8)
    - 2001 Study Guide Originals, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 12/9)
    - EveryWoman's Delegation Study Guide Originals 2003, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 12/10)
    - Articles-Original, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 12/11)
    - Cuba Delegation 2001, 2000 (Box-folder 12/12)
    - Association for Women's Right in Development Conference + Cuba Delegation/ October 2002, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 12/13)
    - Association for Women's Right in Development (AWID), 2002 (Box-folder 12/14)
    - Pamphlets, 2001 (Box-folder 12/15)
    - Pamphlets, miscellaneous, 2002 (Box-folder 12/16)
    - National Women and Cuba Collaborations, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Every Woman's Delegation/ April 2001, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 12/18)
    - Every Woman's Delegation- Local/National Network, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 12/19)
    - Publication, Miscellaneous, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - Small Pamphlets/handouts, 2001-2007 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - Miscellaneous: Event Flyers, Correspondence, Peace & Freedom Magazine (Spring 2006), Defense Statements, and Materials about Cuba, 2001-2007 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - Name list, 1992 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - Institute for Global Security Studies (IGSS) Financial, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 13/5)
    - IGSS: Board, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 13/6)
    - Program Committee, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 13/7)
    - Membership/Fundraising campaign, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 13/8)
    - Women Conference, 1992 (Box-folder 13/9)
    - Charles Conference Materials, 1992 (Box-folder 13/10)
    - Grants and Project Information, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 13/11)
    - 1990- W3 forms & W2 information, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 13/12)
    - Washington Department of Revenue, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 13/13)
    - Board Members, 1991 (Box-folder 13/14)
    - Membership 1992 (Box-folder 13/15)
    - Peace Mission, 1990 (Box-folder 13/16)
    - IGSS Board Of Directors Handbook, 1989 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - U.S. Women & Cuba Collaboration, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 13/18)
    - United State Social Forum 2010 (Box-folder 13/19)
    - Various Event Flyers, United States Social Forum Program Booklet (June 2010), Terra Viva Newsmagazine (Issue 1 and 2, June 2010), 2009-2010 (Box-folder 13/20)
    - Publications, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - Hum Bows Not Hot Dogs, 2001 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - Marguerite Casey Foundation/Aug. 3-5,2005 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - Event Mailers, Correspondence, Filipino American Herald (May 2006 issue), Positive Futures Network State of the Possible Directory of Retreat Participants, Spring 2006 Summit Materials, 1999-2007 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - United States Social Forum - National Planning Committee Dec. 2006 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - Aurora Project, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - EveryWoman's Delegation, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 14/7)
    - Young Eight Experience, 2005 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - National Asian Pacific American Women's Forum (NAPAWF), 2004-2005 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - International Women's Day 2004 (Box-folder 14/10)
    - International Examiner pg 9-12 (April 16-May 6, 2003), The Source (May 2003), International Examiner pg. 1-2, 19-20 (February 5-18, 2003) (Box-folder 14/11)
    - Economy, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 14/12)
    - Clippings, Labor and Employment Office Materials, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 14/13)
    - Cuba, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 14/14)
    - Xerox, 2000 (Box-folder 14/15)
    - Collaboration Retreat April 2004 (Box-folder 14/16)
    - Mailers, Flyers, Newspaper clippings, .45 Kaliber Proof zine (Vol.3, No.2 || Vol.3, No. 3 || Vol. 4, No. 1), Notes, Proposal Application of Women's Alliance, 1979-2007 (Box-folder 14/17)
    - Miscellaneous Cuba, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 14/18)
    - Fifi Flyers, 2002 (Box-folder 14/19)
    - News clippings, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 14/20)
    - Delegation to Cuba, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 14/21)
    - Footsteps of the Revolution Tour, 2002 (Box-folder 14/22)
    - Financial Materials, 2002 (Box-folder 14/23)
    - Women and Cuba, 1995-2002 (Box-folder 14/24)
    - Women's Leadership Summit, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 14/25)
    - LELO EveryWomen's Delegation, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 14/26)
    - Building On Beijing: US NGOs Shape a Women's National Action Agenda booklet, 1997 (Box-folder 14/27)
    - Women, 1998-2002 (Box-folder 14/28)
    - Treatment of Women of Color under U.S. Law, 2001 (Box-folder 14/29)
    - Display in a Prominent Place, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 14/30)
    - Intervention in Venezuela, 2006 (Box-folder 14/31)
    - Booklets, Clippings, Miscellaneous, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 14/32)
    - Notes, Mailers, 1993-2006 (Box-folder 14/33)
    - Firestone Campaign Literature (originally in white binders), 1996-1999 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - Friends for Firestone, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - Campaign/Election Literature (originally in blue binder), 1990-1993 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - Cuba 5, 1996-2003 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - Cuban Publications, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - Local News, 1999 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - C3 Reports, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - Miscellaneous Election, 1999 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - Labor Label Lists, 1999 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - Firestone, 1999 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - Literature other campaigns, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 15/12)
    - Expense Report, Postcards, Mailing List, LJHS Hearing (Tape), Pinoy Teach CD, Marguerite Casey Foundation Interactive Annual Report on CD, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 15/13)
    - Manuscript for A String of Pearls (a Play) - Thomas Churchill, Undated (Box-folder 15/14)
    - Publications, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 15/15)
    - Clippings, 1973-2008 (Box-folder 15/16)
    - Correspondence, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 15/17)
    - Staff Retreat, 2002 (Box-folder 15/18)
    - Article: US Peace and Justice Movement Must Defend Cuba's Sovereignty by Cindy Domingo, c. 2000s (Box-folder 15/19)
    - Press Release, 1993-1999 (Box-folder 15/20)
    - Reading File- May, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 15/21)
    - Church Council Materials, 1984-2008 (Box-folder 15/22)
    - World Trade Organization (WTO), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - Seattle University Reception- November 29, 1999 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - Advancing Women As Leaders, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - December 4 Conference, 1999 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - World Trade Organization pamphlets, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - Criminal Justice 2001, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, printouts (1 of 2), 2000-2005 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, printouts (2 of 2), 1998-2003 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - Call of Nature/September- November 2000 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - Center for Women's Global Leadership, 2001 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - Covert Action Quarterly, 1979-2003 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - Flyers, Handouts, etc., 2000-2004 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - International Examiner, 2003 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - A Memorandum to President Bush, 2005 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - Trips/A Travel Journal, 1999 (Box-folder 16/15)
    - Women and the Media/Delegation to Cuba, 2000 (Box-folder 16/16)
    - Washington Research Council Report/September 2002 (Box-folder 16/17)
    - Women International League/28th Triennial Congress, 2002 (Box-folder 16/18)
    - Peace and Freedom Winter 2004 (Box-folder 16/19)
    - LELO Workshops, 1999 (Box-folder 16/20)
    - Travel Documents, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 16/21)
    - Cuba, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 16/22)
    - Clippings, 1998-2005 (Box-folder 16/23)
    - NW Labor+Employment Law Office, 2002 (Box-folder 16/24)
    - Mujeres, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 16/25)
    - Sangandaan 2003 (Box-folder 16/26)
    - Pista Review, 1981-1994 (Box-folder 16/27)
    - News Clippings- SIlme+Gene, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 16/28)
    - ¡Presente!, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - Cuba Action Day, 2005 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - CIvil Liberties, 2003 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - 2005 WILPF Congress (Box-folder 17/4)
    - Originals, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - Asian-American Information/Present, 2004 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - FIle, 2002 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - Building a Movment for Progressive Taxation, 2001 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - Women Organzing, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - Migrant Filipino Women, 1993-1998 (Box-folder 17/10)
    - Caughlan, John, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - News Article: Marcos Rgime, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 17/12)
    - Notes, Clippings, Addresses, etc., 1986-1992 (Box-folder 17/13)
    - News Articles: Aquino, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 17/14)
    - Sedfrey Ordonez, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 17/15)
    - The Hitachi Foundation, 1992 (Box-folder 17/16)
    - Willie D. Notes, c.1980s (Box-folder 17/17)
    - News Article: Ballot Fraud, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 17/18)
    - "In Search of Despotamia" skit, "Requiem for a Tyrant" songs and lyrics, Audiocasette tape (Side 1: In Search of Despotamia, Side 2:We are the World), c. 1980s-c. 1990s (Box-folder 17/19)
    - News Articles: Marcos Fleeing, 1986 (Box-folder 17/20)
    - Clippings, Flyers, Miscellaneous, 1981-2005 (Box-folder 17/21)
    - Contacts: Community/Organzations, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 17/22)
    - Correspondence: Labor Groups, 1992 (Box-folder 17/23)
    - Miscellaneous, 2000-2008 (Box-folder 17/24)
    - Department of Neighborhood Proposal, 2003 (Box-folder 17/25)
    - Voices of Working Women, 1999 (Box-folder 17/26)
    - Binder Contento (1 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box-folder 17/27)
    - Binder Contento (2 of 2), 2002-2003 (Box-folder 17/28)
    - Socialism: Utopian + Scientific Study Guide, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - Articles: Baruso Verdict, 1991 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - News Articles, 1988-1996 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - Imelda Marcos Clippings, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - Marcos Trial Clippings, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - Publications, 1977-1997 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - Institute for Global Security Studies, 1989 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - 1978 Rank and File Election Committe Slate (Box-folder 18/8)
    - Women & Development Conference (IGSS), 1990-1993 (Box-folder 18/9)
    - Wards Cove - 1994, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 18/10)
    - International Women's Conference- 1995, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 18/11)
    - Counterspy " Assassination of Two Seattle Unionist" March-May 1983, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 18/12)
    - LELO, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 18/13)
    - Churchill Book, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 18/14)
    - Banner, 1995 (Box-folder 19/1)
- Cindy Domingo papers, 1982-1992; 5651-002; 9 cubic feet 9 boxes
  Records relating to Cindy's activism and work as an officer in several organizations including Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes, Line of March, and the Union of Democratic Filipinos (In Tagalog: Katipunan ng mga Demokratikong Pilipino), or KDP.
  Cindy Domingo, 10/31/2011.
  - CINDY DOMINGO PAPERS, SERIES I (Box-folder Box 1-Box 9)
    - Correspondence Legal, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Correspondence Legal (includes an audiocassette mix tape "to joyce from beeman"), 1982-1989 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Maleng's Correspondence, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Correspondence Media, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - Correspondence Outgoing, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - Anti-Racist Community Outreach, 1981 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - Filipino Outreach, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - Women's Community Outreach, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - Mailing Lists- Old, 1982-1988 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - Correspondence "Weird", 1982-1988 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - ACLU, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - Advisory Committee, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - American Friends Service Commitee, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - Amicus Brief of Domingo and Viernes v. Marcos and Republic of the Phillippines, 1983 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - African National Congress Harassment, 1988 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Anti-Marcos, U.S. Surveillance/ Harassment, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - Arab-American Anti-Discrimination Committee Murder, 1985 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Arellano Visit, 1982 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - A Territory Resource, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - Awards Info/Nominations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - Azurin, Joselito, 1979 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - Ballard, Tom, 1989 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - Baruso, Tony, 1980-1989 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - Catholic Archdiocese, 1983- (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Caughlan Fundraiser, 1989 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - Center for Constitutional Rights, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - Central America Movement Harassment, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - Christic Institute, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - Church Council of Greater Seattle, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - Tom Churchill Notes, 1989- (Box-folder 1/30)
    - Civil Rights Cases/Issues Miscellanous, 1989 (Box-folder 1/31)
    - Commission for Justice for Rudy Lozano, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 1/32)
    - Community Meetings, 1981 (Box-folder 1/33)
    - Conyers, John Jr., c. 1980s (Box-folder 1/34)
    - Crackdown in Philippines Background Information, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 1/35)
    - Mark Curtis Case, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 1/36)
    - Dia Circular, 1982 (Box-folder 1/37)
    - Bill Davis, 1980-1987 (Box-folder 1/38)
    - Deposition Summation, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 1/39)
    - Dictado, Tony, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 1/40)
    - Executive Order 12333, 1981 (Box-folder 1/41)
    - Federation for Progress, 1982 (Box-folder 1/42)
    - Forsythe, Levane, 1981 (Box-folder 1/43)
    - Fourth Circuit Appeal, 1987 (Box-folder 1/44)
    - Funding Exchange/National Community Funds, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 1/45)
    - Bonifacio Gillegos, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - Greensboro Justice Fund, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - Guloy, Ben, 1981 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - HBO Movie, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - Hamide, Khader, 1987 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - Hawaii, 1986 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - ILWU Resolution 1981, 1989 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - JACL, 1982-1989 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - Landau, Saul, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - La Pena Bombing, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Letielier Teach-In, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - Letelier Murder, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - Letielier Teach-In Material, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - Liu, Henry, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - Local 37, ILWU, 1982 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - Mike Lowry's Support, 1981 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - Mailman/Tadesco Video Project, 1967-1986 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Malabed, Leonilo, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Maleng, Norm Correspondence/Meetings, 1982 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - Manglapus, Raul, 1987 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - Marcos Visit, 1982 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - Marcos Visit 1982 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - Imelda Marcos on Trial/Seattle Properties, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - Marcos, Ferdinand, 1982-1991 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - 1991 Third World Connection, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 2/25)
    - Event flyers and correspondence, news clippings and newsletters, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 2/26)
    - Memorial 6/90, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - Memorial - 1989 (Box-folder 2/28)
    - Memorial - 1988 (Box-folder 2/29)
    - Memorial - 1986 (Box-folder 2/30)
    - Memorial - 1985 (Box-folder 2/31)
    - Memorial - 1984 (Box-folder 2/32)
    - Memorial - 1983 (Box-folder 2/33)
    - Memorial - 1982 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - National Lawyers Guild, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - National Security/Intelligence Information, 1982-1987 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - Presentation Outline of Larry Sarjeant on National Security, Notes, Articles, and Book Chapter Copies, Undated (Box-folder 3/4)
    - National Committee Against Repressive Legislation, 1983-1990 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - SIster Darlene, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - Ninth Circuit Appeals: Marcos Deposition Decision, 1987 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - Office Opening, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - Palestinian Harassment, 1987 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - Palestinian Deport Cases, 1987 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - Petition to Schultz, 1982 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - Philippines - General Information, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - Philippines - Labor Repression, 1982 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - Philippines Consulate Seattle, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - Philippines Trip - 1986, June, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - "Pinoy" Controversy, 1984- (Box-folder 3/16)
    - Farwest Convention and Philippine National Day Materials, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - Pioneer Alaskero Project, 1985-19864 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - Political Rights Defense Fund, 1987 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - Popular Front Lists, 1987 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - Popular Front, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - Events, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - Propaganda Pieces - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) (1 of 3), 1982 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - Propaganda Pieces - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) (2 of 3), 1982 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - Propaganda Pieces - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) (3 of 3), 1982 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - Regardie's Article, 1988 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - Religious Leaflet, 1982 (Box-folder 3/27)
    - Rewald, Ron, 1984 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - Santos, Jose - Defected Marcos Agent, 1984 (Box-folder 3/29)
    - Santos Event, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - Schroeter, Goldmark & Bender Correspondence and Financial Records, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 3/31)
    - Seminar - April 30, 1983, 1983-1983 (Box-folder 3/32)
    - Seminar - Reading Material, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 3/33)
    - Settlement of Domingo and Viernes Case, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 3/34)
    - Silkwood Case, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 3/35)
    - Silkwood Teach-In, 1982 (Box-folder 3/36)
    - Silkwood Play, 1982 (Box-folder 3/37)
    - Speaking Tour - November, 1982 (Box-folder 3/38)
    - Spectra Communications, 1989 (Box-folder 3/39)
    - Speech - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) meeting ( 8-81), 1981 (Box-folder 3/40)
    - Stationary Originals, Undated (Box-folder 4/1)
    - Copies of Letterheads, Undated (Box-folder 4/2)
    - Steering Committee Notes - Seattle, 1982 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - Taper Media Enterprises, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - Trial Notes, 1990 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - Ver, Fabian General, 1986 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - Victory Party 1/90, 1991 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - Victory Celebrations 1/90 (Seattle/Oakland), 1990 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - Vietnamese Death Squads, 1981-1992 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Vundla, Mfundi, 1986 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - Wolrd Council of Churches Presentation 7/83, 1983 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - Yasui, Holly, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - KGO-TV Documentary "Philippine Spies", 1987 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - The Weekly, 1982 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - Philippines History Book Project, 1983 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - Press Lists - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Press Lists - Originals Local/National [1/2], Undated (Box-folder 4/17)
    - Press Lists - Originals Local/National: Articles [2/2], 1986-1989 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes Frontline 7/87, 1987 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - Hawaii Star Bulletin Articles 11/89-12/89, 1989 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - New York Times Tom Wicker, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - Ang Katipunan Special Reprint "Target: KDP", Undated (Box-folder 4/22)
    - Counterspy: Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes Article, 1983 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - Mcgaffin, Don Editorials, 1982 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - New York Times DIA Circular, 1983 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - American Federation of State, County, Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1983 (Box-folder 4/26)
    - Alaskero News, 1982 (Box-folder 4/27)
    - Ang Katipunan Volume VIII Number 12, 1981 (Box-folder 4/28)
    - Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship/Philippine Solidarity Network Newsletter (CAMD/PSN), 1983 (Box-folder 4/29)
    - 1983 (Box-folder 4/30)
    - East Wing, 1983 (Box-folder 4/31)
    - La Voz, 1982 (Box-folder 4/32)
    - International Examiner, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 4/33)
    - Movement Support Network, 1986 (Box-folder 4/34)
    - Mountain Life and Work, 1982 (Box-folder 4/35)
    - Peoples World, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 4/36)
    - The Weekly - September 1982 (Box-folder 4/37)
    - National Anti-Racist Organizing Committee (NAROC)- Like It Is, 1982 (Box-folder 4/38)
    - National Lawyers Guild Briefs (NLG), 1982 (Box-folder 4/39)
    - Union Democracy Reviews, Undated (Box-folder 4/40)
    - Committee for Justice for Domingo and Viernes (CJDV) Newsletter, 1981-1984 (Box-folder 4/41)
    - Ang Katipunan (AK), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - Alliance Against Women's Oppression Reproductive Rights, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - Anti-Martial Law Coalition (AMLC) 7, 1978 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - Anti-Communist Study, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Asian/Pacific Islander Student Association, 1991 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Bannerman Fellowship, Undated (Box-folder 5/7)
    - Bibliographies, Undated (Box-folder 5/8)
    - Black Liberation Commission Conference August/September 1986 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Black Nation Thesis, Undated (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Black Workers Congress, Undated (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Blue Shield Strike Bay Area, 1980 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Bonifacio, Andres, Undated (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Boston Bussing Issue, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Building the Web Conference 7/88, 1988 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - Caughlan, John, Undated (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Chicago Conference - Electoral Politics, September 1986 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Chile, 1986 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Chinese Garment Industry, 1976 (Box-folder 5/19)